qs = {
    "master": [
        {
            "question": "Which is the value of 15*6?",
            "options": "1.90\n2.80\n3.70\n4.60\n",
            "answer": "1"
        },

        {
            "question": "What is the value of 999+99?",
            "options": "1.2000\n2.1098t\n3.189\n4.100\n",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 1+1?",
            "options": "1.5\n2.3\n3.2\n4.4\n",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 2*2",
            "options": "1.21\n2.0\n3.1\n4.4\n",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 4+6",
            "options": "1.10\n2.30\n3.20\n4.100\n",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 9*100",
            "options": "1.40\n2.900\n3.90\n4.9\n",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 7*7",
            "options": "1.50\n2.51\n3.49\n4.30\n",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 500*10",
            "options": "1.5\n2.50\n3.500\n4.5000\n",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 50/5?",
            "options": "1.10\n2.20\n3.30\n4.40\n",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {   "question": "What is the value of 70/2?",
            "options": "1.50\n2.35\n3.40\n4.20\n",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 70*4?",
            "options": "1.304\n2.504\n3.280\n4.290\n",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {   "question": "What is the value of 80*4?",
            "options": "1.50\n2.100\n3.200\n4.320\n",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {   "question": "What is the value of 60*3?",
            "options": "1.180\n2.160\n3.140\n4.120\n",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 30*3?",
            "options": "1.30\n2.90\n3.20\n4.10\n",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {   
            "question": "What is the value of 70*2?",
            "options": "1.110\n2.120\n3.140\n4.160\n",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {   "question": "What is the value of 30*4?",
            "options": "1.30\n2.60\n3.90\n4.120\n",
            "answer": "4"
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the value of 7%2?",
            "options": "1.1\n2.2\n3.3\n4.4\n",
            "answer": "1"
        },
        {   
            "question": "What is the value of 5*6?",
            "options": "1.20\n2.30\n3.40\n4.50\n",
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 30-20?",
            "options": "1.1\n2.40\n3.10\n4.40\n",
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the value of 20*0.5?",
            "options": "1.40\n2.30\n3.20\n4.10\n",
            "answer": "4"
        }
    ]
}
